Chaoyue Zhao

About Me

My journey with < code /> started about three years ago when I was asked to create an event marketing email. This experience sparked my curiosity and interest in the world of coding. As I continued to dive deeper, I decided to join the HackerYou bootcamp program.

I'm always curious about finding different solutions to a coding problem, learning new frameworks and turning ideas into code. I'm excited about the possibilities of creating art through code using modern CSS and Javascript.

Contact



416-820-3595



chaoyuezhao.com



chao@chaoyuezhao.com



611 - 8 Rean Dr. Toronto, ON M2K3B9

Experience

Mentor

HackerYou College of Technology

February 2019

• In-class resource for students attending Web Development Basics workshop teaching HTML and CSS

Event Manager

Strategy Institute

September 2017 - February 2018

- Managed and executed all logistic aspects for up to 6 conferences simultaneously
- Achieved up to 15% savings within event budget while improving attendee onsite experience

Conference Coordinator

Green Roofs for Healthy Cities

August 2015 - February 2017

- Planned, executed and delivered for more than 20 events, ranging from multi-day conferences with tradeshows to small meetings and workshops.
- Surpassed revenue goals by up to 30% while collaborating with other team members.

Education

Web Development Immersive

HackerYou College of Technology

January - March 2019

Event Management, with Honours

Algonquin College of Applied Arts and Technology

Sepetember 2014 - April 2015

B.A. Communication and Media Studies; Psychology; Minor in Film Studies, with Distinction

Carleton University

September 2009 - April 2014

Skills

- HTML
 CSS/SASS/Styled Components
 Javascript/jQuery
- React Firebase REST API Github/NPM/Yarn
- Acessibility
 VS Code
 Cvent
 Salesforce
 RWD